<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>WTF</title>
    <link>http://wtfutil.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on WTF</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 09 May 2018 11:13:11 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://wtfutil.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Textfile</title>
      <link>http://wtfutil.com/posts/modules/textfile/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 May 2018 11:13:11 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://wtfutil.com/posts/modules/textfile/</guid>
      <description>Description Displays the contents of the specified text file in the widget.
Source Code wtf/textfile/  Required ENV Variables None.
Keyboard Commands Key: h Action: Open/close the widget&amp;rsquo;s help window.
Key: o Action: Opens the text file in whichever text editor is associated with that file type.
Configuration textfile: enabled: true filename: &amp;quot;notes.md&amp;quot; position: top: 5 left: 4 height: 2 width: 1 refreshInterval: 15  Attributes enabled Determines whether or not this module is executed and if its data displayed onscreen.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Newrelic</title>
      <link>http://wtfutil.com/posts/modules/newrelic/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 May 2018 09:01:14 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://wtfutil.com/posts/modules/newrelic/</guid>
      <description>Description Connects to the New Relic API and displays the last n deploys of the monitored application: deploy ID, deploy time, and who deployed it.
Source Code wtf/newrelic/  Required ENV Variables Key: WTF_NEW_RELIC_API_KEY Value: Your New Relic API token.
Keyboard Commands None.
Configuration newrelic: applicationId: 10549735 deployCount: 6 enabled: true position: top: 4 left: 3 height: 1 width: 2 refreshInterval: 900  Attributes applicationId The integer ID of the New Relic application you wish to report on.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Opsgenie</title>
      <link>http://wtfutil.com/posts/modules/opsgenie/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 May 2018 20:53:40 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://wtfutil.com/posts/modules/opsgenie/</guid>
      <description>Description Connects to the OpsGenie API and displays all your scheduled rotations and who&amp;rsquo;s currently on call.
Source Code wtf/opsgenie/  Required ENV Variables Key: WTF_OPS_GENIE_API_KEY Value: Your OpsGenie API token.
Keyboard Commands None.
Configuration opsgenie: enabled: true position: top: 2 left: 1 height: 2 width: 1 refreshInterval: 21600  Attributes enabled Determines whether or not this module is executed and if its data displayed onscreen. Values: true, false.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Security</title>
      <link>http://wtfutil.com/posts/modules/security/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 May 2018 20:33:28 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://wtfutil.com/posts/modules/security/</guid>
      <description>Description Displays some general information about the state of the machine&amp;rsquo;s wifi connection, firewall, and DNS settings.
Wifi Network The name of the current network Whether or not the network uses encryption and if so, what flavour  Firewall Whether or not the firewall is enabled Whether or not Stealth Mode is enabled  DNS Which DNS resolvers (servers) the machine is configured to use  Source Code wtf/security  Required ENV Variables None.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bamboohr</title>
      <link>http://wtfutil.com/posts/modules/bamboohr/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 May 2018 20:17:37 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://wtfutil.com/posts/modules/bamboohr/</guid>
      <description>Description Connects to the BambooHR API and displays who will be Away today.
Source Code wtf/bamboohr  Required ENV Variables Key: WTF_BAMBOO_HR_TOKEN Value: Your BambooHR API token.
Key: WTF_BAMBOO_HR_SUBDOMAIN Value: Your BambooHR API subdomain name.
Keyboard Commands None.
Configuration bamboohr: enabled: true position: top: 0 left: 1 height: 2 width: 1 refreshInterval: 900  Attributes enabled Determines whether or not this module is executed and if its data displayed onscreen.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Clocks</title>
      <link>http://wtfutil.com/posts/modules/clocks/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 May 2018 19:47:31 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://wtfutil.com/posts/modules/clocks/</guid>
      <description>Description Displays a configurable list of world clocks, the local time, and date.
Source Code wtf/clocks/  Required ENV Variables None.
Keyboard Commands None.
Configuration clocks: colors: rows: even: &amp;quot;lightblue&amp;quot; odd: &amp;quot;white&amp;quot; enabled: true locations: # From https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/List_of_tz_database_time_zones Avignon: &amp;quot;Europe/Paris&amp;quot; Barcelona: &amp;quot;Europe/Madrid&amp;quot; Dubai: &amp;quot;Asia/Dubai&amp;quot; UTC: &amp;quot;Etc/UTC&amp;quot; Vancouver: &amp;quot;America/Vancouver&amp;quot; Toronto: &amp;quot;America/Toronto&amp;quot; position: top: 4 left: 0 height: 1 width: 1 refreshInterval: 15 # Valid options are: alphabetical, chronological sort: &amp;quot;alphabetical&amp;quot;  Attributes colors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Modules</title>
      <link>http://wtfutil.com/posts/modules/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 May 2018 18:04:58 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://wtfutil.com/posts/modules/</guid>
      <description>The heart of WTF is the modules. A module is a discreet unit of functionality that extracts data from some source and packages that data for display.
For example, the New Relic module uses New Relic&amp;rsquo;s API to retrieve a list of the latest deploys and packages that information as a list for display in the &amp;ldquo;New Relic&amp;rdquo; widget.
The Clocks module takes a list of timezones and packages that information as a list of city/time pairs for display in the &amp;ldquo;Clocks&amp;rdquo; widget.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Glossary</title>
      <link>http://wtfutil.com/posts/glossary/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Apr 2018 12:34:51 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://wtfutil.com/posts/glossary/</guid>
      <description>Module A discreet unit of data collection and display. A data interface concept. A package inside the app.
Examples: New Relic, Git, Weather.
Widget The onscreen representation of a Module. The widget is responsible for being the interface between the app and the data collection.
Widgets are defined by a required widget.go file in a Module.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Configuration</title>
      <link>http://wtfutil.com/posts/configuration/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Apr 2018 21:17:16 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://wtfutil.com/posts/configuration/</guid>
      <description>Configuration Files By default WTF looks in a ~/.wtf/ directory for a YAML file called config.yml. If the ~/.wtf/ directory doesn&amp;rsquo;t exist, WTF will create that directory on start-up, and then display instructions for creating a new configuration file.
In other words, WTF expects to have a YAML config file at: ~/.wtf/config.yml.
Example Configuration Files A couple of example config files are provided in the _sample_configs/ directory of the Git repository.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>